sketchucation.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy | SketchUcation

## [Privacy Statement](https://sketchucation.com/privacy-policy#privacy-statement)

SketchUcation LLC. has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website [//sketchucation.com](https://sketchucation.com/). SketchUcation LLC. reserves the right to change this privacy statement at any time.

## [System Information](https://sketchucation.com/privacy-policy#system-information)

We use your IP address and browser type to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. This information is used to gather broad demographic information, for operation of the website and to maintain the quality of SketchUcation's services.

## [Cookies](https://sketchucation.com/privacy-policy#cookies)

A “cookie” is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. We use cookies to help us provide personal services and to allow you to sign-in to our site without having to enter your name and password each time (so called "sesion cookies"). Our site uses cookies to keep track of logins, and we may also periodically use cookies as a placeholder for a specific method or process in our system. You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies on your browser. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience this website.

## [Customer Identifiable Information](https://sketchucation.com/privacy-policy#customer-identifiable-information)

Certain functions on this site require users to give us certain contact information. This information is used to help us serve you better; it is shared within our organization but not with third parties. SketchUcation may use this information to contact you to inform you of activities important to the organization. Also, members of any groups in which you affiliate may also contact you about the activities of that group.

## [Internal Use of Information](https://sketchucation.com/privacy-policy#internal-use-of-information)

Our site provides a mechanism for people to send feedback and request more information. This information is not uniquely stored, but may be aggregated with other data to ensure that we properly meet users’ expectations and have the necessary resources planned to accommodate future growth. The person’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the user when necessary. This information is not shared with third parties outside the organization.

## [Security](https://sketchucation.com/privacy-policy#security)

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. This site uses a combination of firewalls, packet filters, security patches, monitoring software, and advanced cryptographic software in conjunction with a secure sockets layer to ensure your personal data is secure from unauthorized access. Only certain employees or volunteers have access to the information you provide us. For example, we impose strict rules on our employees or volunteers who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we try to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

## [Exceptions](https://sketchucation.com/privacy-policy#exceptions)

While we strive to keep and protect our genuine members' privacy and private information, those who deliberately abuse our services acknowledge that their information may be publicly shared on different anti-abuse sites that gather, maintain and also publicly share this information with the widest audience of webmasters and forum management. A prominent example is the [Stop Forum Spam](http://www.stopforumspam.com/) database that we use to protect our site and which we are also an active contributor to.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact [Csaba Pozsárkó](https://sketchucation.com/component/contact/contact/15-management/1-csaba-pozsarko) \- Site and Forum Administrator

Effective: October 1st, 2012
